Denise Weber

(330) 212-1204 dweber0001@gmail.com

Personal Summary

I am making a career change after working in the medical records field for many years. Due to offshoring, my entire QIS team was laid off 11/1/2018, and I was given the opportunity to obtain an associate degree in software development, as part of the Federal TAA program as a displaced worker, which I pursued wholeheartedly! I am now seeking opportunities in which I can integrate my prior work experience with the developer skills I have obtained, and look forward to contributing, learning and growing more in this field. Additional skills I bring: Independent long-term remote worker; positive, empathetic and optimistic attitude; strong multitasking, time-management and communication skills; diligent problem solver; passionate about learning, training, growing and technology.

Work Experience

MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN

July 2003 to November 2018

Quality Improvement Specialist (Remote position)

10/2008 to 11/2018

Duties: Drive Service Delivery excellence for assigned clients via compliance with Quality Program standards utilizing live audits and positive feedback. Perform monthly assigned quality audits for clients (proofreading/editing/scoring). Due to offshoring, my entire team was laid off 11/2018.

Manager, Service Delivery (Remote position)

07/2007 to 10/2008

Managed 5 Supervisors and staff of MTs and QA staff. Daily Goals: Trained/Supported Supervisors to achieve workflow and quality goals, address stat issues. Hiring, training, PMP/PIP, termination. Responsibilities: Performance of Supervisors, MTs and QA staff in attaining TATs, quality, and customer service goals for the 105 hospitals/clinics in our book of business. Company restructure 10/2008: Elimination of all Manager Roles; I was retained in the Quality Improvement Specialist role.

QA Manager/Audit Supervisor (Remote position)

07/2003 to 07/2007

Managed 32 FTE QA Specialists. Developed QA plan to address quality issues/TAT and increase QA production. Promoted 06/2006: Audit Supervisor N Region as part of new national team. Duties: interview, hire, train team of 15 auditors. Lotus Notes Audit DB administrator. Developed training materials, led webinars, trained new auditors, liaison for database users. Promoted to Manager, SD.

EDiX Corporation - Clearwater, FL

August 2001 to July 2003

Medical Transcriptionist/Quality Editor (Remote position) - Transcribed medical reports for all specialties maintaining quality standard requirements for all reviews. Promoted to Quality Editor in October 2002, achieving 4-star monthly reviews for each period.

Education

Sinclair Community College - Dayton, OH

Graduated with Honors. Cumulative GPA of 3.41

Certificates: • IT Fundamentals 08/2020 • Fast Track Programming 12/2020

Responsive Web Design Developer Certification

September 2021

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/denise_weber/responsive-web-design

Links

My Portfolio: https://deniseweberdev.com My GitHub: https://github.com/dweber0001

Skills

- ASP.NET (1 year)
- C++ (1 year)
- JAVASCRIPT (1.5 years)
- NODE.js/NPM
- HEROKU

- BOOTSTRAP
- CSS3 (2 years)
- PYTHON (<1 year)
- REACT (<1 year)
- MongoDB

- C# (1 year)
- HTML5 (2 years)
- jQuery
- FLASK/JINJA2
- SQL/NoSQL

Additional Skills

- Medical terminology, proofreading, editing, reporting. (10+ years)
- Team building, coaching, leading virtual teams, training, assessing performance, managing performance issues, PMP/PIP, hiring, setting goals. (5 years)
- MS Office products, research/analysis, small business accounting, QuickBooks. (proficient)